There is a sincere desire to compete and be part of the team,
他们真诚渴望参与竞争并成为团队的一员
and injuries sidetrack a lot of those intentions.
而伤病 却成了困扰他们的难题
My name is Phil Wagner and I'm the CEO and founder of Sparta science.
我的名字是 Phil Wagner 我是 Sparta science 的首席执行官与创始人
Our goal is to provide a solution for any individual that's looking to be
我们的宗旨是
active and really reducing and preventing the injuries that tend to occur.
为希望主动减少并防止可能发生的伤病的人提供解决方案
When I started noticing strains behind injuries,
我最开始对伤病原理进行研究时
I guess I wasn't thinking about data first,
首先考虑的并不是数据
because I think like most good practitioners I was thinking about the individual first,
因为我认为 和大多数优秀的医生想一样 我首先想到的也是个人因素
and how to avoid the frustration and
如何避免受挫
the emotional pain of enduring a setback like an injury.
以及与受伤一样忍受挫折的情感上的痛苦
One of the defining characteristics of that is the data that that individual produces.
其中一个明确的特征是个人因素产生的数据
The force plate analysis looks at ground reaction force.
我们的应力板主要研究的是地面反作用力
So, when you're jumping and you put force down it causes you to go up.
跳跃的时候 你只要向下施加力量 应力板就会让你跳起来
So, more force into the ground allows you to jump higher.
而且你向地面施加的力量越多 跳得也会越高
And those patterns are what we call movement signature.
这些模式就是我们所说的动作记号
And that movement signature has been linked to
而且 这种动作记号
different injury risks and different performance capabilities.
与不同的伤病风险和不同的表现能力息息相关
The value of good data and really longitudinal data is you can start to identify trends,
良好的数据与真正的纵向数据 它们的价值在于 你可以用来发现趋势
you can start to become predictive of which exercises and
预测哪些练习
training programs are going to be most of
与训练计划
effective at reducing or rehabilitating that injury.
会在减少或恢复伤病方面最有效
So, we work with Stanford University,
所以 我们与多所大学合作 如斯坦福大学
University of Pacific, Brigham Young University among several others.
太平洋大学 杨百翰大学等
And what those relationships provide is really statistical expertise to
与这些大学合作可以为我们带来统计学专业知识
identify how to continue to refine our assessment processes to be more reliable.
帮助确定如何继续完善我们的评估流程 从而使其更加可靠
And so, what makes us different is we've been able to
因此 我们与众不同的地方在于
reduce insurance premiums for universities
我们能够降低这些大学的保险费
to save professional teams' money by having less days lost due to injury.
通过减少因伤病而损失的天数来为专业运动团队节省开支
And so, really having those kinds of results and that kind of impact,
而且 我们真正实现了这样的结果与影响
that is what makes Sparta unique.
这就是 Sparta 的独特之处
At the end of the day the value we're providing is not coming from having a force plate,
最后 我要说的是 我们提供的价值不是来自应力板
it's really from the datasets.
而是来自数据集
So, we want to invest in the framework for software engineers to build that,
因此 我们希望通过投资软件工程师框架来构建这个数据集
and from data scientists to continue to make meaning out of those datasets.
并通过数据科学家继续对这些数据集进行分析研究
For me it all began thinking about,
对我来说 要想实现这一切 首先要考虑的是
how do we address and help each individual person?
我们如何帮助每个人？